<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Melissa G Wolf</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Melissa G Wolf</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cv/</guid>
      <description>Education Doctoral Candidate in Education, Emphasis in Quantitative Methods
University of California, Santa Barbara
Advisor: Andrew Maul
Master of Arts in Research Methods and Statistics
University of Denver, 2017
Advisor: Kathy Green
Graduate Certificate in Measurement, Statistics and Evaluation
University of Maryland, College Park, 2012
Advisor: Gregory R. Hancock
Bachelor of Arts in Communication
University of Delaware, 2009
Minors: Psychology, Anthropology
Research Publications   Wolf, M. G. (in preparation). Lies, damn lies, and survey responses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/preprints/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/preprints/</guid>
      <description>Selected preprints or publications Survey Item Validation
Abstract
In the social sciences, validity refers to the adequacy of a survey (or other mode of assessment) for its intended purpose. Validation refers to the activities undertaken during and after the construction of the survey to evaluate and improve validity. Item validation refers here to procedures for evaluating and improving respondents’ understanding of the questions and response options included in a survey. Verbal probing techniques such as cognitive interviews can be used to understand respondents’ response process, that is, what they are thinking as they answer the survey items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
When you click the Knit button a document will be generated that includes both content as well as the output of any embedded R code chunks within the document. You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars)## speed dist ## Min.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/spss-to-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/spss-to-r/</guid>
      <description>Like many others applied quantitative researchers, I learned statistics on the point-and-click software SPSS. However, when I wanted to transition to R, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find any material that demonstrated how to do an analysis in SPSS and R simultaneously.
As the TA of our intro stat sequence, I&amp;rsquo;ve begun creating labs that include instructions in SPSS (point and click) and the corresponding R script necessary to produce the same output. If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in transitioning from SPSS to R, I hope you&amp;rsquo;ll find this helpful!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Hugo XMin</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>XMin is the first Hugo theme I have designed. The original reason that I wrote it was I needed a minimal example of Hugo themes when I was writing the blogdown book. Basically I wanted a simple theme that supports a navigation menu, a home page, other single pages, lists of pages, blog posts, categories, tags, and RSS. That is all. Nothing fancy. In terms of CSS and JavaScript, I really want to keep them minimal.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>